# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rake db:seed (or created alongside the db with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
# cities = City.create([{ name: 'Chicago' }, { name: 'Copenhagen' }])
#   Mayor.create(name: 'Emanuel', city: cities.first)
# Post.create(title:'First', body:'post')
# Post.create(title:'Second', body:'post')
# Post.create(title:'Third', body:'post')
# Post.create(title:'Fourth', body:'post')
# Post.create(title:'Fifth', body:'post')

Question.create({ question_name: '1st US President', question_body: 'Who was the first US President?', answer: 'George Washington', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '2nd US President', question_body: 'Who was the second US President?', answer: 'John Adams', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '3rd US President', question_body: 'Who was the third US President?', answer: 'Thomas Jefferson', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '4th US President', question_body: 'Who was the fourt US President?', answer: 'James Madison', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '5th US President', question_body: 'Who was the fifth US President?', answer: 'James Monroe', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '6th US President', question_body: 'Who was the sixth US President?', answer: 'John Quincy Adams', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '7th US President', question_body: 'Who was the seventh US President?', answer: 'Andrew Jackson', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '8th US President', question_body: 'Who was the eighth US President?', answer: 'Martin Van Buren', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '9th US President', question_body: 'Who was the ninth US President?', answer: 'William Henry Harrison', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '10th US President', question_body: 'Who was the tenth US President?', answer: 'John Tyler', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '11th US President', question_body: 'Who was the eleventh US President?', answer: 'James K. Polk', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '12th US President', question_body: 'Who was the twelfth US President?', answer: 'Zacchary Taylor', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '13th US President', question_body: 'Who was the thirteenth US President?', answer: 'Millard Fillmore', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '14th US President', question_body: 'Who was the fourteenth US President?', answer: 'Franklin Pierce', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '15th US President', question_body: 'Who was the fifteenth US President?', answer: 'James Buchanan', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '16th US President', question_body: 'Who was the sixteenth US President?', answer: 'Abraham Lincoln', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '17th US President', question_body: 'Who was the seventeenth US President?', answer: 'Andrew Johnson', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '18th US President', question_body: 'Who was the eighteenth US President?', answer: 'Ulysses S. Grant', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '19th US President', question_body: 'Who was the nineteenth US President?', answer: 'Rutherford Hayes', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '20th US President', question_body: 'Who was the twentieth US President?', answer: 'James Garfield', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '21st US President', question_body: 'Who was the twenty-first US President?', answer: 'Chester Arthur', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '22nd US President', question_body: 'Who was the twenty-second US President?', answer: 'Grover Cleveland', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '23rd US President', question_body: 'Who was the twenty-third US President?', answer: 'Benjamin Harrison', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '24th US President', question_body: 'Who was the twenty-fourth US President?', answer: 'Grover Cleveland', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '25th US President', question_body: 'Who was the twenty-fifth US President?', answer: 'William McKinley', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '26th US President', question_body: 'Who was the twenty-sixth US President?', answer: 'Theodore Roosevelt', subject: 'US History' })
Question.create({ question_name: '27th US President', question_body: 'Who was the twenty-seventh US President?', answer: 'William Howard Taft', subject: 'US History' })
